컴퓨터에 뭐라고 나오는진
모르겠지만
Listen, sir, for the last time,
I don't care what the computer says.
우린 바에서 땅콩과자를
사먹은 적도 없고
We did not take a bag of Mashuga Nuts
from the minibar.
'절 죽여 주세요'도
보지 않았다니까요
And we did not watch
Dr. Do-Me-A-Little.
- 어젯밤에 우리 방에 왔었어?
- 아니
-Joey, were you in our room last night?
-No.
청구서에 영화제목은
안 나온다고 했잖아요
I was told the name of the movie
would not appear on the bill.
- 신혼부부인데, 체크아웃할게요
- 맞아, 난 이제 신부가 아니야
-We're checking out of the bridal suite.
-That's right, I'm no longer a bride.
이제부터 신부가 아니라
누군가의 아내가 됐어
I'll never be a bride again.
Now I'm just someone's wife.
난 최고로 행복한 남자야
And I'm the happiest guy in the world.
서운해하지 마
좋은 일도 많이 생길 거라고
Honey, don't be upset. We still have
so much to look forward to.
퍽도 많겠지
Yeah, right.
- 신혼 여행도 남았어
- 목요일에 가잖아
-We got the honeymoon.
-That's not till Thursday.
- 결혼식 사진도 보고
- 몇 주 후에나 나오잖아
-The wedding pictures.
-It won't be ready for weeks.
일회용 카메라도 찍었잖아
Not the disposable cameras
from the tables.
맞아, 이런 점 때문에
너와 결혼한 거야
That's true.
I knew I married you for a reason!
사진을 현상해 올 테니
집에 들어가 있어
Tell you what, I will go get them
developed, and you can go home.
- 뭘 찍었는데?
- 아무것도 아냐
-What? What did you take a picture of?
-Nothing.
대단했어
It was something.
로스가 카메라를 가졌는데
체크아웃했나?
Ross has the cameras.
Has he checked out yet?
체크아웃 시간은
오전 12시잖아
Are you joking?
Checkout is not till noon.
- 11분이나 남았어
- 그래서?
-And he has a good 11 minutes left.
-So?
로스는 꼭 1분 전까지
버틴다고
So Ross had never checked out of a room
a minute before he had to.
맞아, 시간을 놓친 적도 있어
One time, when we were dating,
we got a late checkout.
우리가 가진 잠자리 중
그때가 최고였어
He got so excited,
it was the best sex we ever had.
마지막에 호텔 이름을 외쳐서
기분이 잡쳤지만
Until he screamed out "Radisson"
at the end.
내가 카메라를 받아서
현상해 올게
Okay, well, I'm gonna get Ross,
get the cameras and get them developed.
조, 이제 넌 32살이야
32, Joe. You're 32!
- 영수증입니다
- 감사합니다
-Here's a copy of your bill.
-Thanks.
샴페인, 딸기...
Champagne, strawberries..
이런! 챈들러가 신혼 첫날밤에
포르노를 신청했다니
Oh, my God! I can't believe Chandler
ordered porn on our wedding night.
그래, 안됐군
땅콩과자 먹을래?
Yeah, that's sad.
Mashuga Nut?
프렌즈 시즌 8
'빨간 스웨터'
아직 6분 남았어요!
I have six minutes left!
나야
It's me.
비누, 샴푸?
그걸 전부 가져가려고?
Soaps, shampoos.
Are you really taking all this stuff?
안 될 것도 없지
숙박료에 포함된 거라고
Why not?
It's built into the price of the room.
필요하지도 않잖아
이건 또 뭐야?
Yeah, but you don't need..
What is this?
실이야
Thread.
탁월한 선택이야!
Score!
- 일회용 카메라는 어디 있어?
- 카메라라니?
-Where are the disposable cameras?
-What cameras?
- 어젯밤 내가 챙기랬잖아
- 네가 언제?
-Last night I asked you to take them.
-No, you didn't.
케이크 자르기 전에
내가 너한테...
Yes, remember?
Right before we cut the cake, I said..
네가 부탁을 하려던 참에
Yeah, you asked me
if I could do you a favor.
머레이 삼촌이 와서
계산서를 주셨지
Then my Uncle Murray came up to you
and handed you a check.
넌 계산서를 계산기라고
부르면 안 되냐고 했어
Then you said, "Why is it called a check?
Why not a Yugoslavian?"
그러자 삼촌은 무척 황당한
표정을 지으셨지
Then you did that,
and my Uncle Murray looked at me like:
- 카메라가 없다고?
- 그렇다니까
-So you don't have the cameras?
-No, sorry.
모니카가 난리를 칠 거야!
So, what? They're gone?
Monica's gonna freak!
호텔에 있을 테니 찾아보자
I'm sure they're here somewhere.
I'll help you look.
- 좋아
- 3분 후에
-Great.
-In three minutes.
아직 챈들러가 안왔잖아
Are you gonna open the presents
without Chandler?
그게 아니라...
No! I'm just..
선물들이 열어달라고 재촉했어
이 녀석은 무릎까지 올라왔어
They're calling out to me.
This little guy even crawled up in my lap.
하나 정도는 괜찮을 거야
이건 뭘까?
Chandler wouldn't mind if I opened just
one present. What do you think it is?
자신의 얼굴이
늙어 보이는
A little mirror that,
when you look into it..
작은 거울
you see yourself as an old woman.
작은 소금통이야
A tiny salt shaker!
작은 소금을 넣지
Oh, my God, for tiny salt!
정말 대단해
역시 재미있단 말이야
Oh, wow! Okay. Well, that was fun.
That was fun.
나머지는 챈들러가 오면
뜯어 봐야지
Okay, I'll just wait for Chandler
to open up the rest of them.
소금통은 소금, 후추통 세트의
일부니까
Although, you know, this is part
of a salt-and-pepper set.
반이나 다름없어
내 말이 맞지?
It may just count as only half a present.
What do you think?
나머지 반도 찾아야 돼
이거 같아
I guess it's okay to open one more if it's
part of a set. It's probably this one.
이거 같기도 하고
Or this one!
- 안녕, 현기증은 없어?
- 남자애들은 모르지?
-How are you? Got any morning sickness?
-The guys don't know yet, do they?
챈들러는 임신한 사람이
피비인 줄 알아
Joey and Ross don't know anything.
Chandler thinks Phoebe's pregnant.
맞아, 내가 임신한 줄로
알고 있지
That's right.
Chandler does still think I'm pregnant.
헌데, 가방을 들어준다고
말한 적도 없어
He hasn't asked me how I'm feeling
or offered to carry my bags.
그와 결혼할 여자가
불쌍하다니까
I feel bad for the woman
who ends up with him.
네 다음 사람 말야
After you, of course.
몇 시간만 더 임산부 행세를
하면 돼
Don't worry. You only have to be
pregnant for a few more hours..
오늘 애 아빠에게 알릴 거야
because I'm telling the father today.
이 건물에 살아?
1층에 사는 키 큰 남자?
Is it someone in the building?
That tall guy on the first floor?
- 아니야!
- 귀엽던데
-No!
-What? I think he's cute.
- 네가 그의 아기를 가지면 되겠군
- 나도 노력 중이야
-Then you have his baby.
-Believe me, I'm trying.
참 이상하다
넌 오늘 말해 줄 건데
It's so weird.
You're gonna tell this guy today..
그는 상상도 못하고 있지
and he has no idea
what's gonna happen.
넌 불쑥 찾아가 그의 인생을
송두리째 바꾸겠지
You're just gonna knock on his door
and change his life forever.
복권 당첨 사실을
알려주는 사람처럼 말야
You're like Ed McMahon,
except without the big check.
돈이나 성적 매력이 없지만
Or the raw sexual magnetism.
맞아, 큰 소식일 거야
Yeah, well, I guess
it is pretty big news.
큰 정도가 아니라고!
청천벽력과 같을 거야
Pretty big? It's huge!
God, this guy doesn't have a clue.
"내가 레이첼 그린과 잤어
난 대단한 놈이야!"라고 생각할테지
He's just walking down the street thinking,
"I had sex with Rachel Greene. I rock!"
그러다 애 아빠가 되면서
모든게 달라지겠지
Then, bam! He's a father,
everything's different.
그가 애 아빠가 되기를
원할 때의 얘기지
It's only different if he wants it to be.
I'm not gonna ask him for anything.
그래도 큰 결정을 내려야 하잖아
He still has this huge decision
to make.
"아빠가 되고 싶은가?"
생각하다가, 쾅!
Now he's walking around thinking,
"Do I want to be a dad?" Then, bam!
"쾅"은 뭐야?
What was that "bam"?
버스같은 거에 치는 소리겠지
I don't know.
He's hit by a bus, or something.
너와 잔 여자가 임신 사실을
알리면 어떡하겠어?
Joey, what would you do if someone you
slept with told you she was pregnant?
누가 전화했어?
Who called here?
목소리가 어땠어?
전화 좀 해야겠어
Did she sound blond? Did she have
an accent? I gotta make a call.
선글라스 가게에
들어가는 게 아니었는데
Should have never walked
into that Sunglass Hut!
네 얘기가 아니야
아무도 전화하지 않았어
It's not you!
You didn't get anybody pregnant.
간떨어질 뻔했잖아
대체 무슨 일이야?
Why would you scare me like that?
What the hell's going on?
누가 임신했어?
Is somebody pregnant?
응, 나야
Oh, yeah! That's me.
세상에, 피비!
아기를 낳을 거야?
Oh, my God, Pheebs!
You're gonna have a baby?
응, 낳아서 기를 거야
Yes, I am.
Oh, my God, I'm gonna have a baby!
- 아빠는 누구야?
- 넌 모르는 사람이야
-Wait a minute, who's the father?
-You don't know him.
그는 나와 아기와
연관되고 싶어하지 않아
It's not important. He wants nothing
to do with me or the baby.
대체 어떤 녀석이야?
내가 혼쭐을 내 줄게!
Who is this guy? Because I will
track him down and kick his ass!
- 데이빗 린이야
- 그랬군!
-David Linn.
-David Linn!
- 그게 누구야?
- 내 헬스클럽에 다니는 짜증나는 남자
-Who's David Linn?
-Some guy from my gym. Little annoying.
- 챈들러?
- 카메라 찾았어?
-Chandler?
-Did you find the cameras?
- 아니, 넌 찾았어?
- 응
-No. Did you?
-Yes.
그래서 테이블 밑에서
자축하는 거야
That's why I'm under the table,
celebrating.
분실물센터에 가 봤는데
습득물이 없다더군
I checked in the lost and found. I talked
to the manager. No one's turned them in.
큰일 났어, 모니카를 기쁘게 할
유일한 거였는데
Great. Those cameras were the only thing
that was gonna cheer Monica up today.
신혼이 왜 우울하대?
You just got married.
Why is she so depressed?
그걸 묻지 않으려고
최대한 노력하고 있어
All my energy is going
into not asking that question.
- 일을 망쳐 버리다니
- 미안해
-I can't believe I screwed this up!
-I'm sorry, man.
좋은 생각이 있어
여긴 똑같은 연회장이고
Here's a thought.
This is the same ballroom.
차려입은 사람들도
많이 몰려올 거야
There's a band. There's gonna be
plenty of dressed-up people.
춤추면서 떨쳐버리란 소리야?
Are you suggesting
we dance our troubles away?
천만에, 카메라를 다시 사서
턱시도를 입고
No, I'm saying we buy more of these
at the gift shop..
다시 찍잔 말이야
throw our tuxes back on
and take a few pictures.
얼굴만 안 나오면 되지
We just have to make sure
not to get anybody's faces.
진심이야?
Are you serious?
신부가 걱정돼서 그래
I'm thinking about
your new bride at home.
신혼 초기부터 부인을
실망시킬 작정이야?
Do you want to start your life together
by letting her down?
결혼 상담이야?
네가?
Marriage advice? Really?
너희 결혼식 때와
똑같다니까
I'm telling you,
this looks exactly like your wedding.
- 똑같은 꽃이야?
- 몰라, 모니카가 골랐거든
-Aren't these the same flowers?
-I don't know. Monica picked them.
- 의자는?
- 의자도 마찬가지야
-What about the chairs?
-Those too.
- 테이블의 식기는?
- 그것도
-The place settings?
-Her.
- 넌 뭘 했어?
- 난 카메라 담당이었어
-What did you do?
-I was in charge of the cameras.
상점으로 가자
Gift shop?
- 얘기했어?
- 아직
-Did you do it yet?
-Not yet.
여기서 뭐 하는 거야?
지금 말하려고?
Then what are you doing here?
Are you about to do it?
혹시 건더야?
Is it Gunther?
- 그 사람은 아니야!
- 저런 머리의 아기가 아니라 다행이야
-It's not Gunther!
-Thank God. Because that hair on a baby?
애아빠는 여기 없어
아직 말 못했어
The father is not here, okay?
I haven't told him yet.
- 말할 자신이 없어
- 왜?
-I don't think I can tell him at all now.
-Why not?
"애아빠에게 알려줘야지"
그리고 쾅!
I was walking down the street, thinking,
"I'm gonna tell the father." And then, bam!
버스에 치었어?
Bus?
너 때문에 무서워졌어
큰 충격일 거라고 했잖아
No, you! You freaked me out.
You kept saying how huge this all is.
사실이잖아
But it is huge.
난 내가 받은 충격만
생각하고 있었어
I know. But I was just thinking about
how huge it was for me.
애아빠의 입장은 모르고
I didn't even go to how huge it'll be
for the father.
그에게 속시원히 털어놓고
끝내버리라고
You're thinking about this way too much.
Just tell him and get it over with.
반창고를 떼는 것처럼
아프지도 않을 거야
It's like ripping off this Band-Aid,
quick and painless. Watch.
맙소사
Oh, mother of..!
내 말이 맞지?
See?
- 선물을 개봉하는 거야?
- 이걸 괜히 열어봤어
-Are we opening presents?
-No. I shouldn't have even opened these.
조이, 난 통제불능이야
부탁 좀 들어줘
Joey, I am out of control!
You have to do me a favor.
내가 무슨 짓을 해도
No matter what I say,
no matter what I do..
선물을 뜯지 못하게
말려줘, 알았지?
please, do not let me open
another present. Okay?
하나만 더 뜯자
Give me one more.
왔구나, 피비
저기...
Oh, good, you're here.
Pheebs? Listen..
- 할 얘기가 있어
- 그래
-Sit down, I got something I wanna say.
-All right.
세상은 험난한 곳이야
특히 미혼모들에겐 말야
It's a scary world out there,
especially for a single mom.
난 항상 우리가 특별하다고
생각해 왔어
I've always felt that you
and I have a special bond.
그래서 말인데...
So..
피비 부페
나와 결혼해 줄래?
Phoebe Buffay, will you marry me?
맙소사!
Oh, my God!
청혼을 수락할게
Oh, yeah, I'll marry you.
- 안 돼!
- 이봐, 이번엔 내 차례라고
-You can't marry him!
-Hey, lady, your day's over. It's my turn.
- 왜 안된단 거야?
- 난 결혼할 거야
-Why can't she marry me?
-I can and I will.
임신한 사람은 얘가 아니라
레이첼이란 말야
She's not pregnant.
Rachel's the one who's pregnant.
세상에
Oh, my God!
9달 후에 가 보면
알게 될 거야
He'd notice when you didn't
have a baby in nine months!
조이잖아
It's Joey!
사랑해
I love you.
레이첼이었다고?
애아빠는 누구야?
Wait, I can't believe it!
Rachel's pregnant? Who's the father?
우리도 몰라
We don't know.
- 그 친구 같아
- 짚이는 사람이 있어
-I wonder if it's that dude.
-There's a dude?
누군데?
Who is it?
한달 전에 레이첼과
밤을 보낸 사람이야
About a month ago
this guy spent the night with Rachel.
얼굴은 못 봤지만...
I didn't see who it was, but..
이야기 끝이야?
Was that story over?
이걸 두고 갔어
The guy left this.
이런, 맙소사!
누군지 알아
Oh, my God!
I know who the father is.
이야기들 좀 끝마치고 가
People have got
to finish their stories.
안녕하세요?
Hello.
가까이 붙어
I don't know if we're both in.
Come closer.
애프터셰이브를 잘했군
Nice aftershave.
가방에 8병이나 챙겨놨는데
하나 줄까?
If you want some,
I've got eight mini bottles in my bag.
- 사진 좀 찍어 주실래요?
- 그럼요
-Excuse me, could you take a picture of us?
-Of course.
저희도 찍어 주시겠어요?
Would you take one of us?
그럼요
Yeah, sure.
찰칵
Click.
- 소리가 안 났어요
- 전 들었어요
-It didn't click.
-I heard it.
- 플래시가 안 터졌어요
- 왜 안 찍어 주나요?
-But there was no flash.
-Why won't you take our picture?
찍어 드릴게요
Oh, yeah. I'll take your picture.
렌즈를 가렸잖아요
Your finger was covering the lens.
댁이 사진작가
엔젤 아담스라도 돼요?
Who are you, Ansel Adams?
Get out of here!
네게 겁준 게 미안해서
Look, I feel really bad about
how I freaked you out before..
애아빠에게 말할 수 있는
자리를 마련했어
so I asked the father to meet you here
so you could tell him.
뭐? 잠깐만
누군지 어떻게 알았어?
What? Wait a minute.
How do you even know who the father is?
내가 멍청해 보이긴 하지만
I may play the fool at times..
질리지 않는 엉덩이를 가진
미인만은 아니라고
but I'm more than a pretty blond girl
with an ass that won't quit.
이 옷의 주인이 맞지?
I believe this belongs
to the father of your baby..
이런, 세상에
그 사람이 와 있다고?
Oh, God. He's in there right now?
그냥 돌아갈래, 아니면
들어가서 반창고를 뗄래?
You can turn around, or you can go rip
the Band-Aid off. What do you want to do?
- 떼 버리자
- 진심이야?
-Let's rip.
-Are you sure?
- 피비!
- 미안해
-Phoebe!
-Okay. Sorry.
레이첼
Hey, Rach.
올라가서 연설하는 장면을 찍을게
Why don't you go up on-stage.
I'll get a picture of you doing the speech.
1995년식 라세이버의 차주께선
프론트로 와 주십시오
Will the owner of a 1995 Buick LeSabre
please see the front desk?
견인 준비 중입니다
Your car is about to be towed.
접니다!
That's my car!
- 95년식 라세이버?
- 맞아요
-A '95 LeSabre?
-Yes.
- 녹색?
- 그렇다니까요!
-A green LeSabre?
-Yes!
- 참, 청색이었어요
- 맞아요, 청녹색이에요
-I'm sorry, I meant a blue LeSabre.
-Yes, green-blue.
빨리 빼지 않고 뭐 해요?
Well, go. Go move it!
마지막 사진을 찍어야지
도망칠 준비해
Ready for the last picture?
Get ready to run.
결혼을 축하드립니다
Congratulations on your wedding.
무슨 일이죠?
So, what's this about?
레이첼이 할 말이 있데요
Rachel has something
she wants to tell you.
이 빨간 스웨터가
당신의 옷이 맞죠?
And I believe that
this is your red sweater.
이건 내 옷이에요
No, this is my red sweater.
이런
Oh, no.
커피 마실 사람 있어요?
Could I get anyone a coffee?
독약이라도?
나 혼자 마시죠
Or poison? No? Just for me? Okay.
어떻게 된 일이야?
What's going on, Rach?
아무것도 아니야
피비가 실수를 했어
Nothing.
Phoebe kind of made a mistake.
그 스웨터를 자주 입는군
무슨 내기라도 했어?
But you do wear that sweater a lot.
Are you involved in some kind of dare?
피비가 불러서 기뻤어
I'm actually glad Phoebe called.
난 많이 성숙해졌어
예전의 내가 아니라고
I know we broke up because you thought
I was immature, but I've grown up.
다시 만나고 싶어
I think we should get back together.
시기가 안 좋아
It's just not the right time.
지금이야말로 적시야
난 준비가 됐어
It is the right time.
I'm ready for more.
레이첼, 다시 노력해 보자
Come on, Rach.
Let's give it another try.
나 임신했어
I'm having a baby.
- 가도 돼
- 고마워
-You can go.
-Thank you.
왜 뜯겨져 있지?
I don't know how
any of these got opened!
- 전부 네가 뜯었어?
- 내가 그렇지 뭐
-You opened them all?
-I know, I am a terrible person.
챈들러가 다신 나를
믿지 않을 거야
Chandler's never gonna trust me
with anything ever again.
우리 부모님이 준 선물이야
You got my parents' gift.
- 그게 뭔데?
- 살라미와 연관된 거래
-What is that?
-I think it does something to salami.
- 어떻게 됐어?
- 태그가 뭐래?
-How'd it go?
-What did Tag say?
태그가 아니었어
조이도 알아?
Tag is not the father.
And Joey knows now?
나도 알고 있어
네가 임신했다니 기뻐
I do, Rach, I do.
And I am so happy for you.
내 브라를 벗기려 하지도 않네
Wow, you didn't even try
to unhook my bra.
- 끝까지 안 밝힐 거야?
- 나중에 때가 되면 말할게
-So are you ever gonna tell whoever it is?
-I will. I'm just not up for it tonight.
녀석이 뭐라고 하든
넌 혼자가 아니야
No matter what this guy says,
you're not gonna be alone in this.
- 정말?
- 그게 말야...
-I'm not?
-No. Listen..
세상은 험난한 곳이야
특히 미혼모들에겐 말야
It's a scary world out there,
especially for a single mom.
난 항상 우리가 특별한 사이라고
생각해 왔어
I've always felt like you and I have
this special bond, you know?
- 레이첼 그린, 나와 결혼할래?
- 뭐?
-Rachel Greene, will you marry me?
-What?
- 뭐라고?
- 뭐야?
-What?
-What?!
- 피비, 반지 돌려줘
- 싫어!
-Pheebs, give me the ring back.
-No!
조이, 말은 정말 고맙지만
남편이 필요한 게 아니야
Joey, you're so sweet, so sweet, honey.
But I'm not looking for a husband.
이해해
I understand.
괜찮다면, 난 누워서
쉬고 싶어
Well, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to go and lie down.
날 방금 거절했잖아
이제 비겼어
What? I proposed to you.
It balances out.
난 상처받았어
I can't say that didn't hurt.
그래도 청혼을 다시 받아줄게
But I'll take you back, Joey Tribbiani.
- 난 말이지...
- '살라미 도우미'다!
-Listen, about that, I only offered..
-Ooh, a Salami Buddy!
맞았어!
There you go!
- 우리가 왔어
- 어서 와
-We're back!
-Great.
우린 부엌에 있었어
계속 부엌에 있자
We're hanging in the kitchen.
Let's stay in the kitchen.
- 사진이 나왔어
- 마음에 들 거야
-It's picture time.
-You're gonna love these.
이건 로스고
Here's a picture of Ross.
이건 나군
And that's me.
이건 로스와 나야
And that's me and Ross.
이건 부부로서의
첫 키스 장면이지
And here's a picture of our first kiss
as a married couple.
사진이 잘 나왔어
Wow, that is a great picture. Yeah!
그것 참 이상하군
카메라가 가방에서 나왔어
And interesting, because I found
the cameras in one of our bags.
돌발상황이군
Didn't see that coming.
첫 키스는 첫 키스인데
So this isn't a picture
of our first kiss..
이 여자와의 첫 키스군
but it is a picture
of my first kiss with this lady.
네 표정을 보니
이 사진은 필요없겠어
Which, by the look on your face, I'm sure
you'll remember, so there's no need..
- 진짜 사진을 뽑아 올게
- 좋은 생각이야
-I'll take the real pictures to get developed.
-Good idea.
먼저 개봉한 거야?
선물은 같이 뜯어야지
You opened all the presents without me?
We were gonna do that together.
다른 여자와 키스했어?
You kissed another woman?!
- 피차일반이군
- 맞아
-Call it even?
-Okay.
- 난 꽃을 물에 담글게
- 예식장에서 훔쳐왔어?
-I'm gonna go get these in some water.
-You stole those from that wedding?
호텔 로비에서 가져왔어
포르노와 과자 값을
No, the hotel lobby. They think they can
charge me for some dirty movie..
숙박료에 청구했으니
골탕 좀 먹어 보라지
and a bag of Mashuga Nuts,
they got another thing coming!
내 스웨터잖아
Hey, my sweater!
한 달 넘게 찾았다고
I've been looking for this
for, like, a month.
맙소사
Oh, my God!
세상에
- 잘 지냈어요?
- 오랜만이군요
-Hey, how you doing?
-Good. Long time no see.
- 스웨터가 멋져요
- 네 옷도 마찬가지야
-Like your sweater.
-Right back at you.
- 레이첼 소식은 충격이에요
- 걔가 원래 그렇잖아
-It's crazy about Rachel.
-Well, she's one crazy lady.
- 누구 거래요?
- 글쎄, 이탈리아 사람이겠지
-So whose is it?
-I don't know, some Italian guy.
네 상표를 보면 알잖아
이상한 녀석이군
Come on, read your own label.
See you later. He is so weird.